Captain Li,
I know
what your expressions will be
when I tell you all this.
You must be shocked
by that pervert Gao Yuhai,
and despise me for bowing to money.
But I had no choice.
I really needed the money.
What this money can bring
is not just helping Song Yanfei
finish a dance drama.
It brings
the continuation of my youth,
loyalty to my dreams,
and infinite imagination
for a beautiful future.
Why did it stop?
This Gao Yuhai...
On the surface, he looks decent.
A star entrepreneur
and a famous philanthropist.
He does everything from student aid
to poverty alleviation.
Who knew he played so dirty
behind closed doors,
keeping a main wife and taking concubines.
He really thinks he's
some authoritarian figure
from a feudal society.
I remember reading a report about him,
saying
his first wife died early,
he hasn't remarried in 30 years,
and he goes to the old house
every Saturday to pay his respects.
His companionship with his late wife
moved so many people back then.
I think so.
The recording stopped.
There are still several files left.
Should I continue?
Sorry,
I got too emotional just now.
Honestly,
if the story had ended here
without any deviations,
and I had successfully
gotten the prize money
and helped Song Yanfei
finish his dance drama,
maybe none of what followed
would have happened.
I don't know
which big shot came out of nowhere,
but I didn't even make it
to the top three.
I only got
an Excellence Award.
It's a total joke.
The performance just now
was so good.
It was beautiful.
I'm back.
Shen Xi, you are amazing.
Yeah, Shen Xi.
Who could compete with you
for the championship?
You're so impressive.
Thank you.
I heard
you're teaching at this school.
I'm planning to sign up when I have time.
You have to guide me when you're free.
Here you go again.
Let's exchange contact info.
We can hang out often.
I heard
your boyfriend is preparing
a dance drama recently.
Can you bring us along?
Of course.
We can work together
to make the dance drama even better.
Okay.
Then let's go together.
Except for Shen Xi,
all other performers
go wait in the lounge next door.
Hurry up.
What do you want now?
Don't worry.
I won't do anything to you again.
I'm here
to give you a heads-up
about something.
Whether it's you or your boss,
I won't see either of you again.
If it's about that,
save your breath.
If it were about that,
it would be simple.
I came to tell you
that you're no longer the champion
of this competition.
What do you mean?
Explain yourself.
A big shot from above
suddenly came
and gave a list.
So you mean
I can only get the prize money
for second or third place?
The top three have all been arranged.
But
if you want,
we can give you an excellence award.
Are you crazy?
I know
in the eyes of you rich people,
I'm just a plaything
you can manipulate at will.
But I've done everything
I should and shouldn't have done.
Don't push me too far.
Where is Gao Yuhai?
I'm going to find Gao Yuhai
and get this straight.
What are you doing?
Let me go.
I have something to say.
I've figured it out.
The ranking doesn't matter.
All I want is the prize money.
As long as you give me the money,
I can pretend I never participated.
Did you offend someone?
What do you mean?
Because a big shot explicitly said that
you,
Shen Xi,
cannot win this competition,
including the prize money.
Otherwise,
Wending Group will be in trouble.
Hello,
all you young,
promising,
energetic
future dancers.
I'm so happy to see you all.
I instantly feel
ten or twenty years younger.
Thank you.
Sorry
for being so incoherent.
Where was I?
I was talking about
leaving the celebration party.
Feng Shu was right.
Exposing his dirty deeds in public
wouldn't do me any good.
People might not even believe it,
and I'd just be putting myself
in the pillory first.
So...
I chose to leave quietly.
I didn't leave to run away,
but to meet someone.
She came to me
right after the competition.
Shen Xi,
Actually, at that time,
I really wanted to find someone
to vent my frustrations to.
I'm Gao Yayan.
I just presented the award to you.
I just didn't expect...
Gao Yayan,
that person
to be Gao Yuhai's daughter.
Gao Yuhai's daughter,
the heiress of Wending Group, right?
But Gao Yayan shared her story,
I used to study dance too.
which truly made me feel her sincerity.
That's why I understand you.
And in a way,
you're actually better off than me.
Can we talk?
Before I went,
I was thinking,
if I was pushed too far,
I'd tell his daughter all the dirty things
her dad did.
If she was just like her dad,
I'd expose them both.
But who knew?
After hearing about her upbringing,
I strongly resonated with her.
I realized
that she hasn't had it easy
all these years either.
We really
hit it off that day.
Plus,
she was
very interested
in Song Yanfei's dance drama.
So I called Song Yanfei over.
That night,
listening to Song Yanfei
talk so excitedly about the dance drama,
I suddenly figured it out.
As long as the goal is achieved,
what difference does it make
if the money comes
from Gao Yuhai
or his daughter Gao Yayan?
But just when
everything was getting on track,
the blows
kept coming one after another.
First,
it was that set of photos.
You're back.
You have a sharp nose.
You're back right after
I finished the last soup.
Go wash your hands for dinner.
What's wrong?
Why are you just standing there?
Go wash your hands.
By the way,
did the contract signing
with Yayan go smoothly today?
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
Did Yayan back out?
That's impossible.
She promised just fine a few days ago.
I'll call her.
Shen Xi,
I don't know
when Feng Shu took
those photos,
let alone how they ended up
in Song Yanfei's hands.
Here,
have some water.
That day,
I drank the water Feng Shu gave me.
And then I couldn't remember anything.
Yanfei,
listen to me.
I...
Explain.
I'm listening.
Why?
Tell me why.
I did it
for you.
For the dance drama.
For me?
For the dance drama?
What are you doing?
Did you resist them
like this too?
You slut!
Don't call me that.
I did it for you.
They said
if I didn't do it,
they wouldn't give me the championship
or the money.
And the result?
Did you get the championship?
Did you get the prize money?
I don't know why this happened.
Fengshu said
a big shot
pulled some strings to get someone in,
and asked if I had offended anyone.
I really don't know why this happened.
You actually did bring money back.
I remember now.
That was your fee for sleeping
with Gao Yuhai, wasn't it?
Leave nothing on.
The money Song Yanfei mentioned
was the cash
Gao Yuhai gave me that night.
Fine,
I'll strip.
Open your eyes.
Look at me.
But we haven't even
reached the finals yet.
Where did you get so much money?
I borrowed it from a friend.
Go rent the rehearsal space first.
I'll pay him back
when I get the prize money.
Borrowed?
What kind of friend
would lend you this much?
Don't worry about it.
This is enough for the rental.
He's been a good friend of mine for years.
He's from a rich family.
Money isn't an issue.
Starring (in stroke order of surnames)
Li Xingchen, Yu Xiaotong
Gao Yayan, Zhang Keying
Special Appearance
(in stroke order of surnames)
Xiao Ze, Wang Hao
Feng Shuwen
Jiang Dahai, Liu Zheting (Liu Zheting)
Cast (in stroke order of surnames)
Forensic Doctor, Cheng Gong
Li Xingchen's Classmate, Liu Haohan
Young Li Xingchen, Li Yuanche
Zhao Wenjuan, Li Ziying
Lead Singer, Xu Weina
Xiao Ze's Father, He Meng
Xiao Ze's Mother, Zhao Yu'en
Assistant, Bai Zhihao
Xu Jiayue
Wang Shiwei
Zhao Wenjuan, Li Ziying
Special Female Classmate, Yue Yue
Li Xingchen's Classmate,
Tang Tang, Dai Guoming
Woman, Sun Meili
Shareholder, Huang
Bird-walking Grandpa, Wang Jiasheng
Waiter, Liu Jiaqi, Dai Guoming
Daughter, Zhang Qiying
College Student
Surveillance Police, Qin Zhiqiang
Xiao Ze's Mother, Pei Xiao
Stagehand Xiao Zhang, Li Chen
Police Colleague, Li Lijun
Female Secretary, Qian Duoduo
Mr. Zhao, Liu Junjie
Injured Person, Xu Ganggang
Scrap Yard Boss Zhang, Li Chenghu
Company Head, Bai Yongjun
Woman, Liu Yutong
Wu Zeyu
Female Nurse, Bai Wanting
Guo Xinye
Speaker Nancy, Xu Ziyi
Speaker in Black, Zhu Yiqi
Bai Xiaosi's Stand-in, Zhao Peng
Yan Yongmei, Li Tianjun
Hu Zexuan
Cleaner, Liu Li
Wang Yanmin
Crew
Chief Presenter, Xu Yue
Hai Ziqing
Guo Guo
Chief Planner, Li Meina
Chief Distributor, Hu Kaichen
Police Consultant / Original Story, Fu Jun
Production Team
Chief Producer
Producer
Production Manager
Life Producer, Yin Zhongheng
Stagehand Team
Yang Qunbao
Kitchen
Kitchen Manager, Yin Xiumei
Vegetable Washer, Hu Xiuxia
Li Zhiwei, Ma Yuan
Zheng Xiaorong
Hu Lei, Qiao Xueyue
Zhang Haiping, Cao Yongjie
Screenwriter: Yue Shunming
Executive Director: Sui Chenggong
Script Supervisor: Li Ting
Casting Coordinator: Kang Hairu
On-Set Assistant Director: Liu Haohan
Sound Department
Production Sound Equipment Provided by
Beijing Wenhui Qiming Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
Sound Assistants: Wu Yingxue, Zhang Qichun
Co-Production Designer: Gong Xueyuan
Prop Designer: Zhang Xueqi
Property Master
On-Set Supervisor
Camera Department
Director of Photography: Li Yixu
Camera A Operator: He Yong
Camera A Assistant
Camera B Assistant: Cao Xing
Camera C Operator: Ma Mingguo
Aerial Cinematographer: Zhan Yuchen
BTS Videographer: Li
Lighting Department
Lighting Director: Gao Yun
Styling Department
Wardrobe & Makeup Supervisor: Ma Yi
Hair & Makeup: Yuan Zihan, Wang Peng
On-Set Hair & Makeup: Liu Lu, Guo Xinye
On-Set Wardrobe Supervisors:
Zhang Lei, Yi Junli
Beijing This Is Cola Culture
Media Co., Ltd.
Marketing Director: Li Yiyi
Project Coordinator: Zhao Zihan
Post-Production
Colorist: Niu Xuerui
Opening Titles
Editor: Zhang Xinyu
Effects Editor: Zhang Xiaoman
Visual Effects
Production Supervisor: Gao Dong
VFX Executive: Jin Linxin
Shang Chenyao
Music Production
Music Director: Xiao Zhuang
Score Production: Xiao Zhuang, Wang Dafu
Music Coordinators:
Jiang Zheng, Liu Zining
Guitarist: Liu Zining
Cellist: Zi Long
Score Mixing: Zhao
Vocal Recording: Zheng Suyang
"Brothers"
Composer: Xiao
Producer: Xiao Zhuang
"Song of Spring"
Singer: Zhang Keying
Children's Vocals: Zhang Maolin
Lyricist: Yue Shunming
Arranger: Xiao Zhuang
Producer: Xiao Zhuang
"Promise"
Lyricist: Bai Yuxiang
Producer: Xiao Zhuang
Gao Jingman
Composer: Xu Yue
"That's All"
Producer: Xu Yue
"Half a Beat Slow"
Singer: Xu Yue
Arranger: A
Singer: Wang Weijia
"Only You" (Russian)
Shiyan Public Security Bureau
Shiyan Hengjiu Kanghua Real Estate
Co., Ltd. (Longcheng Mansion)
Hubei Zesheng Property Service Co., Ltd.
Shiyan Mingxin Huizhi Dance Academy
No. 88 Gongyuan Road, Zhangwan District,
Shiyan City
Exclusive Social Media Platform
Chief Partner Media
Co-Production Company
Sichuan Prism Chuangjie Film &
Television Culture Co., Ltd.